thank you HR Asia my name is Matthew
Chang I'm the Chief Human Resources
officer of manual life signo cam
Insurance Company this award means a lot
to me and I would like to share this
award with my beloved team uh without
their support without their hard works
we won't get this recognition we won't
get this award and this means that you
know for our people agenda for our
people strategy we work on the right
direction and it's a recognition to all
our efforts in man life signal camp we
believe that the home management we
actually jointly believe that uh we are
building a great place for our employees
to work to learn and to grow thank you